888media.net 2013-06-06

# 888media - Delivering Results - Privacy Policy

Updated on June 17, 2011 

888 Media is a technology-enabled media services company whose clients and customers include both online advertisers ("Advertisers") and Internet content sites ("Publishers"). We deliver innovative products and services designed to: 

Enable Advertisers to better reach their target audiences; and  
Enable Publishers to support, grow and monetize their websites through the sale of advertisements.

We believe that safe, secure and respectful practices regarding the use of consumer information are fundamental to our business success and to the growth and vitality of the Internet as a whole.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide consumers with clear and complete information about the consumer data we collect in connection with our Services and the way that data is stored and used by our company, our Advertisers and our Publishers.

**Information We Collect**

Non-Personal Information Collected by our Services

We deliver advertisements from hundreds of Advertisers across a multitude of Publisher websites. When you visit one of the Publisher websites in our network, our automated system may collect "click stream data" related to your visit to the website. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as your IP address, Web pages viewed, the date and time at which those pages were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those Web pages. Technologies used to collect this click stream data, include cookies and Web beacons.

In order to improve performance, we augment our click stream data with non-personally-identifiable behavioral and demographic data from Publishers and other partners. This anonymous data may include such things as zip code, age, gender and income range.

We utilize the non-personal information described above to better customize the sort of advertisements you see. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data in order to identify large audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to the most relevant Internet audience. We store the information collected in log files, and log files are retained in our systems for a reasonable period of time. Anonymous data stored in our log files that associates the log data to a particular computer include IP address and User ID. We purge the IP address and irreversibly obfuscate the User ID from our log files six months after collection of this information.

We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information you have disclosed to us in response to judicial process or court order or to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation of matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

**International Transfers of Data**

Personally identifiable information collected by 888 Media may be stored and processed in the United Kingdom or any other country in which 888 Media or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or customers maintain facilities. You acknowledge and agree that personally identifiable information you provide to us may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. Providing such information will constitute your consent to any such transfer.

**Information Security**

888 Media follows generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to, destruction or disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic and management activities required to protect data integrity, access and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential and is not made generally available to the public. Our servers are protected by firewalls and are located in secure data facilities to further increase security. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

**Transfer of Data Upon Change of Control**

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all data (including any personally identifiable data) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party.

**Children's Privacy**

888 Media is sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Hence, our services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. We don't offer the targeting of advertising towards anyone under the age of 13.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on this page. The date on which the current Privacy Policy was posted will always be noted at the top of this page. Any change we make to our Privacy Policy will be made in compliance with applicable law.

**Correspondence**

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including your email address. This relates to your correspondence with us only - we do not gather users' email addresses as part of our online advertising business. 

**Questions and Comments**

Questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to **admin@888media.net**
